# LUIS ROCHA: FRONT-FND WFB DEVELOPER.

<u>luisrochadev.com</u> <u>luisrochaphoto.com</u> <u>luisrochadev@gmail.com</u> (619) 699-9854

### **SUMMARY**

Frontend web developer with a passion for design. Skilled in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Angular. Proficient with the Adobe Creative Suite. Obsessed with producing intuitive and aesthetically pleasing user experiences. Clean, responsive, mobile-first design above all else.

#### **SKILLS**

Front-end development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
Front-end frameworks & libraries (Angular, Bootstrap, jQuery, SASS, WordPress)
Back-end development (Node.JS, Express)
Testing & deployment (Mocha, Heroku)
Tools (Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, NPM, Gulp)
Adobe Creative Suite (PS, Lightroom, InDesign, etc)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER - Interact Intranet

June 2016 - October 2016

Used WordPress to build, launch, and iterate on digital global marketing campaigns with conversion optimization in mind. Analyzed UI/UX of existing web pages to ensure fully responsive, cross-browser usability. Designed wireframes and mockups of new pages and enhancements.

# **SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER** - San Franpsycho Clothing

December 2014 - September 2015

Increased social media follower count by 40% and customer engagement by 60% in the span of 6 months. Developed new social media strategy to stimulate brand growth and increase sales. Managed published content (images, video and written).

## **STAFF PHOTOGRAPHER** - San Franpsycho Clothing

August 2013 - September 2015

Established brand's visual aesthetic and identity. Worked closely with executive team and designers to conceptualize photoshoots and lookbooks. Prioritized multiple projects to ensure all deadlines were consistently met.

# FOUNDER, PHOTOGRAPHER: Luis Rocha Photography

January 2011 - Present

Self-employed freelancer. Proactively sought out clients and secured contracts with major brands and music festivals including Outside Lands, Coachella, EDC, and more. Created batch-editing scripts to quickly edit large volumes of photos. Established online presence through several social media channels.

#### **EDUCATION**

**GALVANIZE** San Francisco, CA 24-Week Web Development Program

SAN FRANCISCO STATE UNIVERSITY San Francisco, CA